var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The one who",
        "pcklId": "1434",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "Which",
        "pcklId": "1435",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2841",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمَعَ",
        "answer": "collects",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "jamaʿa",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْسَبُ",
        "answer": "Thinking",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "yaḥsabu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُطَمَةِ",
        "answer": "the Crusher",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-ḥuṭamati",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُطَمَةُ",
        "answer": "the Crusher (is)",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-ḥuṭamatu",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْلَدَهُ",
        "answer": "will make him immortal",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "akhladahu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرَاكَ",
        "answer": "will make you know",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "adrāka",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَطَّلِعُ",
        "answer": "mounts up",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "taṭṭaliʿu",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَّدَهُ",
        "answer": "and counts it",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "waʿaddadahu",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَدٍ",
        "answer": "columns",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ʿamadin",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَفْئِدَةِ",
        "answer": "the hearts",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-afidati",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "to every",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "likulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "لُمَزَةٍ",
        "answer": "backbiter",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "lumazatin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُمَدَّدَةٍ",
        "answer": "extended",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "mumaddadatin",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَالًا",
        "answer": "wealth",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "mālan",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَالَهُ",
        "answer": "his wealth",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "mālahu",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيُنْبَذَنَّ",
        "answer": "Surely he will be thrown",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "layunbadhanna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارُ",
        "answer": "A Fire",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "nāru",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُمَزَةٍ",
        "answer": "slanderer",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "humazatin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْصَدَةٌ",
        "answer": "closed over",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "mu'ṣadatun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُوقَدَةُ",
        "answer": "kindled",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-mūqadatu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "104",
        "ayah": "6"
    }
]; 
export default words;